I just refused
Fu Chenzhou
Are you just gonna watch him talk to me about the past
You were free to seek her out
It's her right to reject you
But you can't disguise your late regrets
as deep affection she must return
What if I told you I really
never thought I'd lose you
That makes you even more pathetic
You assumed I'd never leave
while keeping a way out for yourself
You think just because you say you regret it
I'd be touched
She's still waiting for you
President Gu 10 minutes are up
Fu Group's reception area is not meant for
repeatedly dealing with personal drama
Are you really not giving me a chance
No
You really came looking for my sister
Why are you here
What you just said to my sister
I heard all of it
You said you regretted it
And that if you could start over
you wouldn't choose me
Yurou we're at Fu Group's entrance don't make a scene
Hmph